[
    {
        "question": "A warlord serves as an early access to mint  the in-game playable figurines and a/an _____",
        "answer1": "sbt",
        "answer2": "PFP",
        "answer3": "inscription",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the suitable age required to be eligible for the warlord claim ",
        "answer1": "18",
        "answer2": "21",
        "answer3": "16",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are  magical playable figurines in the dark world of Grimori",
        "answer1": "warriors",
        "answer2": "Champions",
        "answer3": "Vikings",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "When will the  Champion verse game be released?? ",
        "answer1": "Early next year",
        "answer2": "Next month",
        "answer3": "Q4 23",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": " Complete the following phrase , From darkness ,___________",
        "answer1": "Champions are born",
        "answer2": "Champions arise",
        "answer3": "Champions rise",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What chain is champion verse launching ",
        "answer1": "Eth",
        "answer2": "Arb",
        "answer3": "Avax",
        "correctAnswer": 1 
    },
    {
        "question": "The two most acceptable or preferred wallet for the warlord mint are metamask and ___",
        "answer1": "Xverse",
        "answer2": "Phantom wallet ",
        "answer3": "Face wallet",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What platform will be supported by the game? ",
        "answer1": "Champions Tacticsâ„¢ Grimoria chronicles ",
        "answer2": "Opensea",
        "answer3": "Magiceden",
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The warlords Comes with a PFP collection of _______ unique digital collectibles",
        "answer1": "666",
        "answer2": "9999",
        "answer3": "9000",
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of game is championsverse",
        "answer1": "FPS",
        "answer2": "action-adventure",
        "answer3": "RPG",
        "correctAnswer": 3
    }
]